cvphysiology.com 2019-05-11

# CV Physiology | Privacy Notice

## Effective January , 2009

### Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

Our Commitment To Privacy   
The Information We Collect   
How We Use Information   
Our Commitment To Data Security   
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy   
How To Access Or Correct Your Information   
How To Contact Us

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and all html pages that use the home page template. 

### The Information We Collect: 

Non-personal information is collected about your computer, such as your IP address and type of web browser, and is used solely by web scripts for compiling site statistics. This information is not linked to you or your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

### The Following Information is Not Ever Requested or Collected:

Credit/Debit Card Information  
Complete Mailing Address  
Phone Number

### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself only for communication within, and in regards to, the forum and relevant website information. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [contact us](mailto:author@cvphysiology.com). 

DISCLAIMER: These materials are for educational purposes only, and are not a source of medical decision-making advice.
